

NHẬT HUY ĐOÀN

Frontend Developer

- 🛗 Sep 14, 1997
- Male
- +84 364051835
- nhathuy97ars@gmail.com
- O Danang, Vietnam
- i https://my-portfolio-sooty-sig ma.vercel.app/

OTHER SKILLS

- Critical Thinking
- Self-study and problemsolving
- Research
- Time Management
- Teamwork
- Using english in work



I'm a Frontend Developer. I'm extremely passionate about web development especially Frontend Development, helping businesses and improving their online presence. In the past, I have studied Automation Engineering at Danang University of Science and Technology (2015 - 2020). Now I have just finished Frontend Development Course at CyberSoft Academy and had nearly 1 year of working experience with frontend languages. Now I currently aim to learn as much as I can in a work environment and to further my own abilities in a professional setting.



EDUCATION

DANANG UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

SEP 2015 - MAY 2020

Major: Automation Engineer

level: Good

CYBERSOFT ACADEMY

OCT 2021 - MAY 2022

Major: Frontend Developer

level: Good



TECNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages:

- Javascript (ES6)

Foreign Languages:

- English (Basic conversation and reading foreign documentation)

• Frameworks/Libraries/Techs:

- HTML, CSS (SASS)
- Bootstrap, Ant design, TailwindCSS
- ReactJS, Redux, Redux-Thunk
- Axios, Postman
- Git, Adobe Photoshop,

- · Soft Skills:
- Presentation skills
- Teamwork
- Technical communication
- Highly adaptable



WORK EXPERIENCE

EPC SOLAR MARCH 2020 - MAY 2021

Electric Engineer



BOOKING MOVIE

APRIL 2022 - MAY 2022

Front-end Developer

Customer

Cybersoft Center

Description

- Booking Movie Tickets Website.
- Link website: https://webmovieg4.vercel.app/
- · Link source:

https://github.com/NhatHuy1409/BCDN05_BaiTapReact_WebMovie_Nhom4

Member

3

Role

- Analyze , design layouts and coding website.
- Process the logic proficient.
- Frontend-Technology: HTML, CSS, ReactJS, Axios, AntDesign, Redux, Redux Thunk, Slick Slider,...



Build website with React JS by F8 Academy	2022
Frontend Developer by Cybersoft Academy	2022
Automation Engineer by Danang University of Science and Technology	2020